BABALWA MBOLEKWA

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Computer Systems Engineering Graduate with experience in Web Development and Customer Service. I offer teamwork and Leadership skills that are paired with creativity and diligence. I enjoy working on exciting projects with other IT intellectuals.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Design Thinking (Figma)
- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript
- Object Oriented Programming and Functional Programming
- Test Driven Development (Jasmine)
- Knowledge of C and Java Programming
- Node.is
- MySQL and Oracle Databases
- Git & GitHub
- Linux (Bash)
- APIs

SOCIAL LINKS AND PORTFOLIO

GITHUB

https://github.com/Babalwa01

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/babalwa-mbolekwa-a16a94147

PORTFOLIO

babalwa01.github.io

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

INTERN - SPACE ENGINEERING

Astrofica Technologies | March 2020 - August 2020

• Training and Introductory skills on how to work with Space Mission Designs and Technologies.

LEARNER TECHNICIAN

Eskom | March 2019 - February 2020

- In-service training as part of University Course completion.
- Worked with SCADA system.
- Performed Western Cape substations' reviews.
- Repaired computer hardware.

ADMIN CLERK & TRAVEL AGENT

Zintu Group (Pty) Ltd | January 2016 - December 2016

- Booked accommodation, flight tickets, bus tickets and shuttles services around South Africa for Senqu sub-district government officials and scholars
- Generated quotations for customers who hired event equipment and logistics.

EDUCATION

UMUZI ACADEMY

September 2020 - In progress National Certificate in Information Technology (System Development) (SAQA ID 48872)

CAPE PENINSULA UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

January 2017 - December 2019 National Diploma in Computer Systems Engineering

MOTHEO TVET COLLEGE

January 2013 - November 2015 National Certificate in Electrical Engineering

STERKSPRUIT CHRISTIAN SCHOOL

December 2011 Matric Certificate